

Contact

07539-279207



58 William Mear Gardens, Norwich, Norfolk, NR1 4PE

https://github.com/George Bastock

Skill Key

Expert

Secured

Proficient

Intermediate

Basic

Testimonials

Kayleigh Hall

Developer Trainer

"Testimonial to be provided by developer. Testimonial to be provided by developer.
Testimonial to be provided by developer. Testimonial to be provided by developer."

Sam Stark

Project Manager

"Testimonial to be provided by project manager. Testimonial to be provided by project manager. Testimonial to be provided by project manager. Testimonial to be provided by project manager."

George Bastock

Front End Developer

Summary

I am a highly motivated and hardworking individual, who is looking to use the skills gained from the Scion Coalition Scheme at Netmatters and over a year of experience to build upon a keen interest and start a successful career as a developer.

My greatest strengths include good organisational skills, grasping new concepts quickly, a massive philomathic who is always wanting to learn and the ability to form good, professional relationships with colleagues and clients. Programming is a massive passion of mine and I look forward to applying my skills in the industry.

Skills

HTML5 500+ hours

Several years of experience both personally and professionally and comfortable with semantic markup and general structuring.

JavaScript 150+ hours

Able to use vanilla JavaScript and JQuery along with multiple libraries to build web functionality.

WordPress 20+ hours

Able to install and manage a WordPress site as well as implementing custom plugins.

SQL 10+ hours

I understand the basic syntax to analyse databases and can produce simple to complex queries. CSS3/SASS 500+ hours

I can handle layouts including all aspects of CSS and confidently use dev tools to rapidly style pages as well as being able to use the SASS framework.

Adobe Photoshop 50+ hours

Experience with photoshop for both illustration and web design making wireframes, concepts and mockups.

Github 15+ hours

I have been using git frequently while working on personal projects as well as projects as part of a team.

ASP.NET/MVC 25+ hours

Comfortable using ASP.NET with HTML, CSS & JavaScript to create dynamic websites.

Treehouse

Treehouse is an online learning community, featuring videos covering a number of topics from basic HTML to C# programming, iOS development, data analysis, and more. By completing courses users can earn points, allowing them to track their progress and see how much they've covered certain areas.

Total Score: 13,750

Profile: teamtreehouse.com/georgebastock

Experience

Work Experience, Aviva UK, Norwich

Software Developer

2017 - 2018

- Complete a series of independent and team tasks under time constraints.
- Significantly improved working on a task as a team under pressure, adapting to unknown software and new technology.

Junior Web Developer , 101 ltd, Taverham

Software Developer

2017 - 2018

- The ability to form good, professional relationships with colleagues and clients.
- Able to manage and prioritise several large projects at a time.

Mcdonalds Chapelfield, Norwich

Crew member 2016 - 2017

- Constantly multitasking customers and orders.
- Improved being able to manage time effectively.

Introduction to Scion Coalition Scheme

The Scion Coalition Scheme is an intensive, specially tailored training program being run by Netmatters in order to give willing candidates the opportunity to enter the industry as web developers. Under the supervision of senior web developers, scions generally aim to complete training within six to nine months. The course is intensive and therefore the level of learning achieved is extensive in a short space of time.

Education

2018-Present

Scion Coalition Scheme

- Undertook an intensive, specially tailored training program under the supervision of senior web developers in the industry. This course is 40 hours per week and simulates employment as a developer to ensure the trainee is prepared for full time employment.
- Studied front-end and back-end development including UI/UX design, mobile development, object-oriented programming and databases.

2017-2018 **Level 3 App**

Level 3 Apprenticeship - Website Development

- I was an apprentice at 101 ltd for website development and app development where I was integrated into the team such as an employee.
- Built multiple websites for real clients using the latest plugins and frameworks.
- Interacted with real clients from start to finish on projects and bounced edits with them.
- Completed: City and Guilds functional skills level 2 ICT.

2016-2017

Sir Isaac Newton Sixth Form

- Studied A level maths, physics and computer science for a year but was unable to complete due to reasons not related to education.
- Predicted A levels : Computer Science (A), Maths (B),
 Physics (B)

2011-2016

Open Academy High School

 9 GCSEs: English (B) Computer Science (A) Information Technology (D*) Maths (B) Science (B) Additional Science (B) Geography (A*) Religious Studies (B) Business Studies (M2)

Hobbies

Virtual Reality

I am a big enthusiast of virtual reality, I have played around with making my own vr headset as well as making several virtual reality games. My most recent project is making a non-euclidean environment so walking in VR feels seamless to your brain.

Literature

I am a keen reader of fantasy from authors such as George R. R. Martin and autobiographies from Chris Kyle. I am currently learning new ways to dramatically enhance my reading ability.

Computing

I have built multiple custom PCs including my current home pc as well as helping friends and family with there's. I love making build lists that get the best performance for value on a set budget.